♪Red harvest comes♪
♪Where can I run♪
杰克归来
♪Had a dream one night♪
原创翻译  双语字幕
■
仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新
请登陆www.ZiMuZu.tv
♪Of a ship breaking free♪
翻译  小肚腩 早先森 信徒
■
♪You stood on the shore♪
翻译  凉粉 showeryhe 人妻
♪Watched me drifting off to sea♪
校对  紫玉
♪Every now and then♪
♪A wave of sadness covered me♪
时间轴 大葱ALX 孙了个大圣 林卡
♪A century of sleep♪
后期 aaaBao  总监 紫玉
♪Can't erase the memory♪
打开微信   扫描左侧二维码
或搜索公众号:    美剧炸了
了解最新影视资讯字幕信息
♪Red harvest comes♪
♪Where can I run♪
♪Stars forsake me♪
♪A cold wind shakes me♪
♪Where can I run♪
♪Red harvest comes♪
他拍下被害人的照片
He photographs his victims.
这是第四个
This one was number four.
每个女人遇害的日期都恰好是
Each woman was murdered 100 years to the day
一百年前开膛手杰克行凶的日子
from the original Jack the Ripper murder.
第一个是在八月三十一日
The first on the 31st of August,
下一个是在九月八日
the next September the 8th,
然后九月三十日有两个
then two on the 30th.
所有被害人都是妓女
All the victims were prostitutes.
尸体被破坏的程度一个比一个严重
Each mutilation was progressively worse
除了第三名被害人
with the exception of the 3rd victim.
她的尸体完全没被破坏
She wasn't mutilated at all,
这也和原始凶案一致
which is the case in the original murders.
这家伙有所准备
This guy did his homework.
今晚是最后一次凶案的日子
And tonight's the anniversary of the last murder?
没错
You got it.
凶案组
警监  这是巴特拉医生
Captain, this is Dr. Battera.
普兰蒂斯警监
Captain Prentis.
很高兴认识你  医生
Glad to meet you, Doc.
你怎么看这个情况
What do you make of all this?
我们得阻止他
We must stop him.
沃利
Wally.
听我说  给他点时间
Look, give him some time.
我们根本没时间了
We haven't got time.
杰克归来
♪这一刻终于到来♪
♪And now the time has come♪
♪我也面对♪
♪And so I faced♪
♪最后落幕♪
♪The final curtain♪
切口应该是在
The incision should be made
右侧腹部下方三分之一处
in the lower 3rd of the abdomen on the right side,
就在这儿下面
just below here.
而且切口要足够大
And should be a sufficient size
让我们能接触到盲肠
to permit access to the intestinal cecum.
我手很大
Now, I have big hands,
但就像我们休斯顿的说法
but like we say in Houston,
伤疤越大  收费越高
the bigger the scar, the higher the fee.
...第五位死者  当局认为
...5th victim, and authorities believe
开膛手今晚会再次行动
the Ripper will strike again tonight.
调频1580  全天全新闻
KBLA, all news, all day.
现在市政中心的气温为三十七摄氏度
It's 98 degrees in the Civic Center right now,
随着圣塔安娜风继续穿过美国南部
with a high of over 100 expected later this afternoon,
预计下午气温将突破三十八摄氏度
as the Santa Ana winds continue across the southland.
海滨区气温三十二摄氏度
It's 89 degrees at the beaches,
山谷区三十九摄氏度
103 in the Valley,
大洛杉矶地区天气预计将会持续
and the forecast for the greater Los Angeles area
晴朗和炎热
is sunny and hot,
-短期不会降温  -好啊  伙计
- with no relief in sight. - What's up, homeboy?
-你好  安德烈  -好啊  约翰
- Hey, Andrea! - Hi, John.
又见到你真好
Nice to see you again.
你好  我是约翰·韦斯福德  欢迎
Hi, John Wesford, welcome.
来这儿的路上遇上什么麻烦没
Did you have any trouble getting down here?
-完全没有  -很好
- Not at all. - Good, good.
整片区域被分成
Now, the whole area here is split up
五块营地
into five separate camps.
我们现在是在佳斯特斯维尔
This one is Justiceville that we're in right now.
我会把你介绍给五位队长
I'm going to introduce you to five captains.
他们每人负责一块营地
Each one oversees a different camp.
我们先去见他们
We'll meet them first
然后晚点就能带你
and then we'll get a chance a little later on
四处看看  希望能拍些画面
to show you around and we can shoot some footage, I hope.
-很好  -好啊  伊曼纽尔
- Great. - Hey, Emmanuel.
汤姆  我现在干什么
So Tom, what do I do right here?
你去把这个转到这儿来
Oh, you have to transfer that down here.
好吗
Ok?
弄完之后  把这个接收到这里
Once you do that, take it over into this.
跟把那个转下来是一样的
Same thing the way you transfer it down.
他在哪儿
Where is he?
他在那个营地  是吧
He's at that camp, isn't he?
大家好  我们今晚的头条新闻是
Good evening, and our top story tonight,
联邦  州及本地警方为搜捕罪犯
the largest mobilization of federal, state and local police
组织的最大规模动员
ever assembled for a manhunt
正就开膛手可能的谋杀之夜
is preparing for what may be another night of murder
进行准备
for the Ripper.
下面是科林·玛希带来的报道
Here's a report from Collin Marsh.
之前就是在回声公园的这条小巷
It was here in this alley, in Echo Park,
警方发现了埃米莉·达特蒙德的尸体
that police found the body of Emily Dartmond,
她是名妓女
a known prostitute,
也是这一系列恐怖凶杀案中的第四位死者
and the 4th victim in this series of grisly killings
这些谋杀的日期分别对应
which mirror the Jack the Ripper murders
开膛手杰克一百年前犯案的日子
that occurred on these same dates 100 years ago.
又来
Not again.
你好  玛丽
Hello, Mary.
你果然没忘
You didn't forget.
西德尼正在找你
Sidney's looking for you.
最好小心点
You better watch out.
没事的  我给他买了玎珰派
That's OK, I brought him some Ding Dongs.
你还好吧  琳达
How you doin', Linda?
这是怎么了
Let's see what we have here.
你叫什么名字
What's your name?
玛莎
Martha.
Martha?
玛丽  能给我点纱布吗
Mary, can I have some gauze?
你有孙子孙女吗  玛莎
Do you have any grandchildren, Martha?
五个
Five.
都叫什么名字
What are their names?
马丁  罗伯特
Martin, Robert,
亚历克西斯  还有珍妮和理奇
Alexis, and Janie and Ricky.
理奇啊
Ricky, huh?
哪个最皮
Which one is the naughty one?
理奇
Ricky.
我跟你说过没
You see, I could've told you that.
我有个哥哥就叫理奇
I got a brother named Ricky
他也是最皮的那个
and he was the naughty one, too.
我想你会没事的
I think you're gonna be just fine,
只需要再缝几针  好吗
you just need a few stitches here, all right?
我们马上就帮你处理
We'll take care of you right away.
下个就是她
She's next.
很好
Great.
谢谢你
Thank you.
周六晚有空吗
Free Saturday night?
诊疗二室
好了
Ok.
告诉你们母亲六周后
Tell your mother that he has to come back
要带他回来卸石膏
in six weeks to get the cast removed.
好的
Ok.
玛丽会帮你们预约
Mary'll make an appointment for you.
好的  谢谢
All right. Thank you.
走吧
Come on.
怎么了  医生
What's up, Doc?
我想有人虐待他
I think he's been abused.
姓什么
What's the last name?
罗文
Rowan.
哈格罗夫大街2330号
2330 Hargrove Street.
家长来过吗
Seen the parents?
一直都是姐姐带他来
His sister always brings him.
看看我们能查出些什么吧
Well, let's see what we can find out, right?
西德尼正在气头上
Sidney's on the warpath.
多新鲜啊
How rare.
他清楚你迟到的原因
He knows why you're late.
我知道  我跟他说了
Yeah I know, I told him.
你跟他说了
You told him?
我要是想听布道  就去找牧师了
If I want to hear a sermon, I'll go see my preacher!
那或许对你还有点帮助
It might just do you some good,
你已经比法定时限晚了两周了
you're two weeks past the legal limit for God's sakes.
面对现实吧
Face the facts.
别到街上去了  懂吗
You stay off the streets, you understand?
你跟拉皮条的说去
You tell that to my pimp.
难道你不在乎肚子里的孩子吗
Don't you care about your unborn child?
韦斯福德
Wesford!
-来我办公室  -稍等...
- In my office. - Just wait...
马上
Now!
约翰  那女人是谁
John, who's that woman?
稍后告诉你
I'll tell you later.
要知道过去两小时我都在
You know I've been doing your work for you
替你干活
for the past two hours.
坐下
Sit down.
你胆子真不是一般的大啊
You got a lotta goddamned nerve, you know that?
外边的人叫你医生
Just because the people out there call you a doctor
不代表你就是了
doesn't make you one.
你还在读医学院
You're still in medical school
在我的监督和批准下
and you're working here
在这里工作
under my supervision and approval.
今天这一出要是再来一次
One more stunt like you pulled today,
我一定会让你
and I'll have your ass bounced out of here
以头晕目眩的速度滚出这里
so fast it'll make your head swim.
听明白了吗
Do you understand me?
我这就写封信给校董会
I'm writing a letter to the Board of Regents.
接下来就当是你的观察期
Consider yourself on probation.
听明白了吗
Do I make myself clear?
明白
Yes.
很好
Good.
你知道  西德尼
You know, Sidney,
病人来这里需要的是帮助
the people that come in here need help,
而不是谴责
not condemnation.
他们的病不是靠
What ails them can't be cured
你那道德感治好的
by some close of your morality.
他们应该被尊重
They deserve the same respect
就像你给予付费病人的那样
that you'd give any paying patient.
你被解雇了
You're fired.
西德尼  你说什么
Sidney, what,
你这里根本没有足够的人手
you don't have enough people out here
来处理该处理的的事物
to take care of the work as it is.
我说你被解雇了  听不到吗
I said you're fired, can't you hear?
好吧  我很抱歉  好吗
All right, look, I-I'm sorry, OK?
西德尼  我跟你说过了我会晚点到
Sidney, I told you I was gonna be late.
这种情况不会再发生了  我保证
It won't happen again, I promise.
西德尼  我想在这工作
Sidney, I want to work here,
我就是在这个街区长大的
I grew up in this neighborhood.
那又怎么样
So what?
听着  我不想为我的行为道歉
Look, I'm not gonna apologize for myself.
有时候  我也有必须要做的事
There are things that I need to do sometimes.
你可真有阿尔贝特·施韦泽的风范  孩子
You know, you're a regular Albert Schweitzer, son.
阿尔贝特·施韦泽 曾到非洲从事医疗援助工作  诺贝尔和平奖得主
我能接着回去工作了吗
Can I go back to work now?
滚吧
Get out of here.
再迟到一次  我就真的解雇你
If you're late again, I will fire your ass.
西德  你那辆弗利特伍德的轮毂盖
Oh, Sid, uh, the hubcaps on your Fleetwood?
不见了
They're gone.
你被炒了吗
Are you fired?
他只是想谢谢我把工作做得这么好而已
He just wanted to thank me for doing such a fine job.
不过他倒是很担心你
He's worried about you, though,
你也是
and you, too.
不想过来看看电视上的你吗
Aren't you going to check yourself out?
老天
Oh, Jesus.
我认为要解决问题不能仅仅靠
And I think that the answer isn't just to build
建立更多的临时庇护所
more temporary shelters.
你希望通过这一举动传递出怎样的信息呢
Well, what message do you hope this effort conveys?
这些人住在这里
That these people aren't here
不是为了给我们提供施善的机会
just to exercise our generosity.
他们之所以来这里  是因为他们无家可归
They're here because they have no home.
我们住在这世界上最富裕的国家
I mean we're in the wealthiest country in the world
却依然有人露宿街头
and people are living in the streets
这是可耻的
and that's a shame.
有一家六口人
You know, you got a family of six
全住在一辆旅行车里  就在那边
living in a station wagon, right over there.
看看你的周围
You know, look around you.
这就是他们的现状  每天真实发生的
This is their reality, every day.
这里是十频道新闻
From downtown Los Angeles,
安德莉亚·班克斯从洛杉矶市区发来的报道
this is Andrea Banks, Channel 10 news.
他来了
Here he comes.
准备好  他来了  他来了
OK, get ready, here he comes, here he comes.
普兰蒂斯警监
Captain Prentis!
普兰蒂斯警监 您今晚要采取什么措施
Captain Prentis, what's your strategy for tonight?
您认为杀手今晚会在哪里下手
Where do you think he'll hit tonight?
整件案子有什么进展
What's being done about this whole thing?
普兰蒂斯警监  有什么新线索吗
Captain Prentis, do you have any new leads?
您认为他今晚会在哪里下手
Where do you think he'll hit tonight?
各位  我已经在
Gentlemen, I made my statement
今早的新闻发布会上发布了消息
at the press conference this morning.
没有进一步消息
I have no further comment.
普兰蒂斯警监 您认为他今晚会在哪里下手
Captain Prentis, where do you think he'll hit tonight?
请您说点什么
Comment, please!
让我们清净一会吧
Yeah, give us a break!
我觉得你们该找地方坐好
All right, I think you ought to grab a seat,
我们准备开始了
we're ready to get started.
后面几位  能坐下来了吗
You wanna settle in back there?
我知道大部分人
I know a lot of you
都是在加班
are working your days off
或是在值第二个班
or pulling a double shift
我想先谢谢大家
and I wanna thank you at the top.
我们得抓住这个混蛋
We need to catch this son of a bitch.
今晚或许是我们最后的机会
Tonight may be our last chance.
加州公路巡警  治安官
Now the CHP's and the Sheriffs
今晚都会有队伍在外面
are gonna have details out there tonight
还有联调局的人
along with the Feds.
我希望你们表现出应有的礼貌
Now I expect you to show them every courtesy,
但我更希望是你们
but I also expect you to be the ones
将这个渣滓绳之以法的
to bring this maggot in.
加布里埃尔警长会向大家介绍案子详情
Sergeant Gabriel's gonna brief you on this detail.
加布
Gabe?
谢谢  警监
Thank you, Captain.
我们了解的情况不多
Well, we don't have much.
正如你们所知  没有幸存者
As you know, there have been no survivors
也没有目击证人
and no eye witnesses.
可以确定的是  几起凶杀案都出自一人之手
We do know that the murders are the work of one man,
还知道凶手是个左撇子的男人
we know that he's left-handed,
他总是戴着手套
he always wears gloves,
他抽烟
he smokes,
而且很强壮
and he's very strong.
作案工具是一把小刀
The murder weapon is a knife,
六到八英寸长  很锋利
six to eight inches long, very sharp,
可能是把手术刀  或者是解剖刀
possibly a scalpel or a post mortem knife.
我们知道这名男子进行了安全性行为
We know that our boy practices safe sex.
他使用带润滑的特洛伊牌安全套
He uses pre-lubricated Trojans.
我们有一些想法
We have a few ideas,
但我想把心理侧写的部分
but I'm gonna leave the psychological profile
交给医生
to the doctor.
你们都有各自的任务
You all have your assignments,
因此现在  我向大家介绍
so at this time, I'd like to introduce
美国心理学会调派来的心理咨询师
Dr. Carlos Battera, our consulting psychiatrist
卡洛斯·巴特拉医生
on loan from the APA.
巴特拉医生
Dr. Battera.
谢谢  加布里埃尔警长
Thank you, Sergeant Gabriel.
开膛手杰克是现代性犯罪的鼻祖
Jack the Ripper was the harbinger,
或者说是开山之人
the father of the modern sex crime
他对我们的凶手影响很大
and he looms large in our subject's mind.
他复制了杰克的每一次作案
He has duplicated each murder
精准到每一个小细节
down to the finest detail.
有的理论认为开膛手杰克是名医生
Some theorize that Jack the Ripper was a medical man
因为其精准的切割
because of the precision of his cutting
以及具有的解剖学知识
and his anatomical knowledge.
我认为这一点同样适用于这个案子
I believe that would also apply in this case.
我能告诉你们最重要的
The most important thing that I can tell you
确定的信息
with any certainty,
很不幸是关于受害者的
is unfortunately about the victim.
她会在自己的房间里被谋杀
She will be murdered in her room
就在未来十二小时之内
sometime in the next 12 hours.
她会是名孕妇
And she will be pregnant.
晚安  各位
Good night, all.
-晚安  玛丽  -晚安  玛丽
- Good night, Mary. - Good night, Mary.
别忘了锁门
Don't forget to lock up.
不会忘的
We won't.
晚安  玛丽
Good night, Mary.
好啊
Hi.
你今晚有些安静
You've been kind of quiet tonight,
没事吧
are you OK?
没事
Yep.
跟今天下午那个女孩有关吗
Have anything to do with that girl this afternoon?
没有
No.
想跟我们说说她的事吗
You wanna tell us about her?
不是很想
Not really.
某人嘴巴很严呢
Cat's got his tongue.
罗杰去哪了  我都没怎么看到他
So where's Roger? I haven't seen Roger.
汤姆  你看到罗杰了吗
Tom, have you seen Roger around?
完全没看到
I haven't seen him around at all.
看来是不会成了哈
Guess it's not happening, eh?
对  没戏
No, not happening.
-罗杰很  -无趣
- Roger is... - Boring.
罗杰很无趣  对吧
Roger is boring, right?
是挺无趣的
He's pretty boring.
不过这也不是你的错
It's not his fault, though.
都是怪他的盎格鲁撒克逊血统
It's all that Anglo-Saxon shit.
两百多年的粗呢外套和领结
I mean 200 years of tweed sport coats and bow ties
把他们的脑子搞坏了
fucks with your mind.
约翰
John.
你能想象他的孩子吗
Can you imagine the kids, though?
一堆小罗杰系着领结
Bunch of little Rogers running around
满地乱跑
with little bow ties.
你俩有完没完
Are you two quite through?
你可是意大利姑娘  生性热情
You're Italian, girl, you've got hot blood.
你该让我介绍个哥们给你
You should let me fix you up with a brother.
最少也找个波多黎各人
At the very least, a Puerto Rican.
我能自己找到男朋友  谢了
I can find my own men, thank you.
好吧
All right.
晚安  克莉丝
Night, Chris.
晚安  杰克
Night, Jack.
谢谢你的书
Thanks for the book.
你喜欢吗
Oh, did you like it?
我还没来得及看呢
I haven't had a chance to look at it yet.
我周末会看的
I'll read it over the weekend.
好的 如果你喜欢的话
Ok. Well, if you do like it, though,
我再给你一本  好吗
I'll get you another, OK?
好啊
Ok.
杰克怎么样
What about Jack?
我觉得他对你有意思
I think he's got a thing for you.
我什么也没说
Didn't hear me.
如果你这么关心我
If you're so concerned about me,
不如你带我出去吧
why don't you take me out?
我
Me?
我们可以共进晚餐
We could go to dinner.
我对你来说太野了  克莉丝
I'm too wild for you, Chris.
你怎么知道  约翰
How do you know, John?
别折磨我了
You're killin' me,
我今晚没法去吃饭  还有工作要做
I can't go to dinner tonight, I've got work to do.
你能带她离开吗  拜托了
Will you get her out of here, please?
当然
Sure.
克莉丝  我送你回家吧
Chris, let me give you a ride home.
开膛手还没抓住呢
The Ripper's still out there.
今晚就会行凶
Tonight's the night.
好  如果你不介意的话
Yeah, if you wouldn't mind.
当然不
Of course not.
晚安
Good night.
车那儿见
I'll see you at the car.
你怎么回事
What's with you?
是男人吗你
Do you have a penis?
闭嘴
Shut up.
明天见  伙计
See you tomorrow, dude.
好
Right.
天啊
Oh, Christ.
你想干什么
What do you want?
我能帮你
I can help you.
怎么帮
How?
我能帮你打掉孩子
I can get rid of it for you.
多钱
How much?
两百
$200.
收支票吗
Take a check?
你收吗
Do you take checks?
让我进去
Let me in.
你要在这儿做吗
Are you gonna do it here?
当然
Of course.
丹妮丝
Denise?
天啊
Oh, my God!
上帝啊
Oh, Jesus!
杰克
Jack!
你做了什么
What have you done?
报警  快报警
Call the police! Call the police!
你这个混蛋  回来
Hey you stupid prick, come back here!
你到底会不会开车
Don't you know how to drive?
有人吗
Hello?
有人在吗
Is anybody here?
快点  快点
Come on! Come on!
紧急事件话务员
Emergency operator.
你有什么紧急事件吗
The nature of your emergency?
我想上报一起凶杀案
Ah yeah, I wanna report a murder.
你的名字
Your name?
约翰  约翰·韦斯福德
John, John Wesford.
W-e-s-f-o-r-d
W-e-s-f-o-r-d.
死者的姓名是丹妮丝·约翰逊
Listen, the victim's name is Denise Johnson
我看到是谁杀了她
and I saw who did it.
不
No!
听着  这不是你想的那样  约翰
Look, it's, it's not what you think, John.
我没有杀她
I didn't kill her!
你得相信我
God, you gotta believe me!
我  我帮她做人流  仅此而已
I-I gave her an abortion, that's all!
我出去给她拿药
Look, I went out to get her prescription.
还不明白吗  一定有别人进了房间
Don't you see? Somebody else must've come in there!
听着  我害怕了  对不起
Look, I got scared, I'm sorry!
我没杀她
I didn't do it!
-你需要帮助  杰克  -不
- You need help, Jack. - No!
天啊
Oh...
该死
Fuck.
上帝啊
Oh, Jesus.
该死
Oh, shit.
普兰蒂斯警监
Captain Prentis!
他是谁
Who was he?
是一名叫约翰·韦斯福德的医学生
He was a medical student by the name of John Wesford.
他上吊自杀了
He hung himself,
他知道我们就快找到他了
he knew we were closing in on him.
我们完成了苏格兰场没能做到的事
Now we've done something even Scotland Yard couldn't do.
我们抓到了开膛手杰克
We've caught Jack the Ripper.
你们有确凿的证据吗
Do you have conclusive evidence?
有
We do.
在案件审理中都会被提出
It'll all be introduced at the inquest.
九点钟在总部我们会召开新闻发布会
We have a press conference at headquarters at nine o'clock.
我相信大家一定都会到场
I trust you will all be there.
借过
Excuse me.
看看能不能在一小时内
Why don't you see if you can get this cleaned up
将这里处理好
in about an hour,
我想要马上看到报告
I want to get a report in to me right away.
好的  市里见  萨姆
You got it. See you downtown, Sam.
好的
All right.
你想吃点儿什么
So where do you wanna eat?
拜托
Oh, boy.
怎么回事
What the hell?
别紧张
Now take it easy.
-这发生什么了  -我们还不能透露
- What happened here? - We still can't talk about it.
我弟弟被谋杀了
My brother was murdered.
-你怎么知道  -我看到的
- How do you know? - I saw it.
你在场吗
You were there?
不  我
No, I...Uh!
我在噩梦里看到的
I saw it in a nightmare.
昨晚
Last night?
是的
Yeah.
跟我说说你在噩梦里都看到了什么
Tell me exactly what you saw in the nightmare.
我
Well, I was,
约翰尼  坐在地板上
Johnny was uh, sitting on the floor, and...
他的脖子上有根绳子
He had a rope around his neck
有人开始拉那根绳子
and someone started to pull the rope.
你看到他的脸了吗
Did you see his face?
没有
No.
你怎么知道
How do you know
你弟弟不是自杀
your brother didn't commit suicide?
我弟弟不是自杀
My brother didn't commit suicide.
有人在那儿伤害了他
Someone who was there hurt him.
有人在他妈的拉那跟绳子
Someone was pulling that fucking rope.
当然
Sure.
你弟弟是左撇子吗  理查德
Was your brother left-handed, Richard?
什么
What?
是的
Yeah.
你呢
Are you?
不  我两手通用
No, I'm ambidextrous.
我去弄点儿咖啡
Let's get some coffee.
你想来一杯吗
Would you like a cup?
好
Yeah.
加奶和糖
Cream and sugar?
可以
Sure.
你怎么看
What do you think?
这个嘛
Well,
要么他说的是实话
either he's telling the truth
要么就是他杀了自己的弟弟
or he killed his own brother.
到底是哪个呢
Well, which is it?
我不知道
I don't know.
确实有资料记载
There have been cases documented
双胞胎能感应到他们兄弟姐妹
where twins knew the exact moment
死亡的那一刻
of their sibling's death.
我想跟他谈谈
I'd like to interview him.
可以的话对他催眠
Hypnotize him if possible.
查查他  看电脑里有什么记录
Run a check on him, see what's in the computer.
跟我来  医生
Come with me, Doctor.
给你
There we go.
理查德  这是巴特拉医生
Richard, this is Dr. Battera.
在这个案子上协助我们
He's been working with us on the case.
你好  理查德
How do you do, Richard?
你觉得我疯了吗
You think I'm crazy?
没有
No, we don't.
我们只是想弄清楚现在的情况
No, we're just trying to clarify the situation.
针对你弟弟
Some very serious charges
有一些非常严重的指控
have been made against your brother.
我们有足够的证据相信
We have enough evidence to believe
他就是开膛手凶杀案的真凶
that he's responsible for the Ripper murders.
我弟弟没有杀人
My brother didn't kill anybody.
有个混蛋在他脖子上套了绳子
Some motherfucker put a rope around his neck
然后把他吊在了该死的天花板上
and strung him up on the fucking ceiling!
我们有目击证人
We have an eyewitness.
去你的目击证人
Fuck your eyewitness.
我不需要这些  好吗
I don't need this shit, all right?
如果你们想让我留下  就拘留我
If you want me to stay, book me.
警长  能不能让我和理查德
Perhaps sergeant, you could give Richard and me
单独待一会儿
some time together?
好吧
All right.
我想帮助你理解
I'd like to try and help you understand
在你身上发生的事  如果你允许的话
what happened to you, if you'll permit me.
昨晚在梦里你看到了发生在你弟弟身上的事
You saw what happened to your brother last night in a dream.
你之前有过类似的梦境吗
Had you ever had a dream like this before?
有过分享疼痛的经历吗
Any shared pain experiences
他受伤然后你感受到疼痛
where he was hurt and you felt the pain?
没有
No.
有没有出现过
Were there any times
你们不需要说话就能交流
that you communicated without speaking?
不管是在一间屋子或是相距很远
Whether in the same room or far apart?
有什么不同寻常的经历吗
Any unusual experiences?
任何事都可以
Anything at all?
有一次  不过是我们六年级的事
Ah, there was one but it was 6th grade.
跟我说说
Tell me about it.
我们的老师给我们考试
Our teacher gave us a test,
历史考试
the history test and uh,
考试结束后
after it was finished,
她把我和约翰尼叫到教室前
she called Johnny and I up to the front of the classroom
说我们作弊了
and said that we cheated.
答案一致  错误一致
Gave the same answers, made the same mistakes.
我们向她解释我们没有作弊
So we told her that we hadn't cheated and uh...
她把我们分到两个房间
she put us into different rooms
又给我们考了一次
and gave us another test.
结果还是一样  完全一致的答卷
And the same thing happened, identical papers.
就这个
That's it.
你接受过催眠吗
Have you ever been hypnotized?
没有
No.
我想对你进行催眠
Well, I would like to hypnotize you.
我觉得也许能让你更加清晰  毫无障碍地
I think it might enable you to see your dream more clearly,
看清梦境
without obstruction.
来吧
Do it.
好
Good.
首先请你把烟掐了
First I'll ask you to extinguish your cigarette, please.
端坐在椅子上
And sit squarely in your chair.
尽可能舒服点
Make yourself as comfortable as possible.
坐在椅子上
In these chairs.
不如把外套脱了吧
Why don't you take your jacket off?
好  我要你集中注意力
All right, I'm going to ask you to concentrate
把所有注意力都集中到
and I'm going to ask you to focus your attention
光点上
on the point of light.
看着光点
Look into the light.
好
Good.
请一直盯着光点
Now, now please, stare at the light.
放松
Relax,
放空思维
empty your mind.
你只能看到光点
You see only the light,
你只能听到我的声音
you hear only my voice.
好了  理查德  你的左臂和木板一样坚硬
All right, Richard, your left arm is as stiff as a board.
好了  理查德  你可以放松你的手臂
All right, Richard, you may relax your arm now
放回你的大腿上
and place it back in your lap.
现在我将带你回到
Now I'm going to lead you back
那间诊所
to the clinic.
周围很黑
It's dark.
怎么了  理查德
What is it, Richard?
告诉我你看到了什么
Tell me what you see.
你看到了什么  理查德
What do you see, Richard?
告诉我你看到了什么  理查德
Tell me what you saw, Richard.
理查德
Richard?
理查德  能听到我的声音吗
Richard, can you hear my voice?
理查德
Richard.
能听到我说话吗  理查德
Can you hear me, Richard,
能听到我的声音吗
can you hear my voice?
不行了
Can't wait.
理查德
Richard!
Richard.
理查德
没事了  理查德  没事了
It's all right, Richard, it's all right.
我看到他的脸了
I saw his face.
天啊
Oh, Jesus.
我看到那混蛋的脸了
I saw the motherfucker's face.
我是十频道新闻的安德莉亚·班克斯
Andrea Banks, Channel 10 News,
你是约翰·韦斯福德吗
aren't you John Wesford?
-他是我双胞胎弟弟  -双胞胎
- He's my twin brother. - You're twins?
你不用理她
You don't have to talk to her.
关于你弟弟是开膛手的指控
Well, what do you think of the allegations
你有什么看法
that your brother was the Ripper?
他为什么自杀
Why did he commit suicide?
他没有  他是被杀的
He didn't, he was murdered.
-你怎么知道  -我看到了
- How do you know? - I saw it.
你是目击证人吗
You were an eyewitness?
-他被拘留在哪里  -他没有被拘留
- Where's he being held? - He's not being held.
警方对此有何看法
What's the police department's position on this?
无可奉告  走
No comment! Move it!
该死
Shit!
以上是十频道新闻的
From police headquarters,
安德莉亚·班克斯在警局总部带来的报道
this is Andrea Banks, Channel 10 News.
我们无能为力  沃利
There was nothing we could do, Wally.
她一直在那候着
She was waitin' for us.
她肯定是昨晚在现场认出他了
She must've recognized him last night at the scene.
我告诉局长  市长
I told the Chief, the Mayor,
以及那帮该死的记者团案子结了
and the whole goddamned press corps the case was closed.
案子可能没我们想得那么简单
Well it may not be as open and shut as we'd like to think.
有些疑点
Something is fishy here
我还需要点时间收集证据
and I need a little time to gather some facts.
证据  我们现在有证据
Facts, now we have facts,
拜托  我们有目击证人  加布
we have an eyewitness for Christ sakes, Gabe!
直接指认了他
That's positive ID.
他身上有死者的血
He was covered with her blood,
全部五名死者在被害前
all five victims were treated at the clinic
都曾在他工作的诊所就诊过
where he worked within days of their murder.
然后那个混蛋自杀了
And the son of a bitch committed suicide.
这案子就这么简单
Now that is open and shut!
现在有个小屁孩做了个梦
And now some kid has a dream,
你们就打算把这些证据抛之脑后
and you want to forget all about it.
那孩子是他的双胞胎哥哥
That kid is his identical twin brother.
他曾出现在犯罪现场
He showed up at the scene of the crime.
他知道他弟弟是怎么死的
He knew how his brother died,
他甚至知道确切的死亡时间
he even knew the exact time of death.
沃利  目击证人可区分不了他俩
Wally, an eyewitness couldn't tell them apart.
刚送到
This just came in.
理查德·韦斯福德的档案
It's Richard Wesford's rap sheet.
大量前科  多是青年时犯下
He's got a whole slew of priors, most of them juvenile.
他曾是王牌帮成员
He was a member of the Aces street gang.
十八岁时被指控破门而入
When he was 18 he was charged with breaking and entering,
用致命武器实施伤害
assault with a deadly weapon.
配合认罪  入军队服役
Copped a plea, went into the Army.
被培养成了军医
They made him a medic.
中了
Bingo.
他在
He works for uh,
第二灵魂运动鞋店工作
the Second Sole athletic shoe store.
大概两个月前从旧金山被调到这
Transferred down here from 'Frisco about two months ago.
就在连环杀人开始前
Just before the killings started.
天啊
Jesus Christ.
双胞胎兄弟是否指纹相同
Do identical twins have the same fingerprints?
我的天啊
Mother Santisima!
我叫理查·韦斯福德
My name's Rick Wesford.
约翰的哥哥
I'm John's brother,
我想打听下有关他的事
I'm looking for some information about him.
有什么事吗
Yes, what do you want?
我叫理查·韦斯福德
My name's Rick Wesford,
我想打听下有关我弟弟的事
I'm looking for some information about my brother.
如果你生病了  我们可以帮你
If you're sick, we can help you.
要打听事  去公共图书馆试试吧
For information, try the public library.
-老兄  你懂的  -少跟我套近乎
- Hey, man, you know this... - Don't "hey man" me.
你要是在这里捣乱
You make any disturbances in here
我就报警  听懂了吗
and I'll call the police, you got that?
懂了
I got it.
走吧
Now get out.
-等等  -回去干活  克莉丝
- Wait! - Get back to work, Chris.
我叫克莉丝蒂娜·莫斯卡莉
My name is Christina Moscari,
我是你弟弟的朋友
I was a friend of your brother's.
克莉丝
Chris!
滚  西德尼
Fuck off, Sidney!
抱歉
Excuse me.
我现在非常忙
I'm really really busy right now,
你愿意的话  晚点我可以和你聊聊
but, but I can talk to you later if you'd like.
我九点下班
I get off at nine.
那到时见
I'll see you then.
谢谢
Thank you.
天啊
Oh, Jesus.
你觉得是他杀了他弟弟吗
Think he killed his brother?
只有这种可能
Had to.
怎么  你真觉得他会什么通灵吗
What, you think he's some kind of swami?
不知道
I don't know.
我奶奶就有阴阳眼
My grandma had the Sight.
这儿又不是阴阳界  萨姆  这可是现实
This isn't Twilight Zone, Sam, this is real life.
我说真的  哥们  玄着呢
I'm telling you, man, it's deep.
-什么事都会有  -天啊
- Shit happened. - Oh, God!
-你好  -好
- Howdy. - Hi.
有间酒吧离这不远  去那谈吧
There's a pub not far from here where we can talk.
好
Good.
车不错
Nice car.
谢谢
Thank you.
怎么回事
What the hell?
他走错道了  萨姆
He's in the wrong lane, Sam!
混蛋
Son of a bitch!
淡定  萨姆
Take it easy, Sam.
他逃不了的
He's not goin' anywhere.
再开差不多三公里  在马路右边
It's up about two miles on the right.
约翰的事我很遗憾
I'm really sorry about John.
他是个好人
He was a good man.
你和他长得真像
You look so much like him.
真不敢相信他已经死了
I can't believe he's dead.
我看到了
I saw it.
我昨晚在噩梦里看到了
I saw it last night in a nightmare.
有人勒死了他
Somebody strangled him,
并把他吊了起来
and then they hung him.
就是这样
That's what happened.
约翰尼没有自杀
Johnny didn't kill himself.
-真不敢相信  -你看到了吗
- I can't believe it! - You see that?
我在电视上见到过
Yeah, I saw him on TV.
以前我们下了班有时会来这
We all used to come here sometimes after work.
你们的诊所里都有些什么药
What kind of drugs do they have at that clinic?
都是一些常用药
Normal pharmaceuticals.
约翰尼能拿到吗
Johnny have access to 'em?
只有西德尼有钥匙
Sidney's the only one with the key.
问这干嘛
Why do you ask?
只是好奇
Just curious.
海伦  这是理查·韦斯福德
Helen, Rick Wesford.
他是约翰的哥哥
He's John's brother.
-你好  -你好
- How do you do? - Hi.
饿了吧  这里的炸鱼薯条很好吃
You hungry? They have great fish and chips.
厨师下班了
Uh, the kitchen's closed.
那就喝点什么吧
OK, we'll have drinks then.
我要蓝带
Pabst for me.
啤酒
Beer.
什么啤酒
What kind?
随便
Any.
你做什么工作  理查
What do you do for a living, Rick?
我负责一家鞋店
I uh, I manage a shoe store.
你说你看到了
What did the police say
凶手的样子  警察怎么说
when you told them you could identify the murderer?
他们不相信我
They didn't believe me.
那你接下来打算怎么办
What are you gonna do?
我自己去找
I'm gonna find him.
谢谢  豪伊
Thanks, Howie.
你和约翰最后一次谈话是什么时候
When was the last time you spoke with John?
我们好多年没说过话了
I haven't talked to him in a couple of years.
你们不是很亲近
So you weren't close, then.
怎么说呢
Well.
以前还行  后来疏远了
We were and we weren't.
抱歉  我想我还是走吧
Listen, I'm, I'm sorry, I better split.
需要送你一程吗
Uh, do you want a ride someplace?
不用
Oh, no.
我住这儿附近  过了桥就是
I live just up the block, across the bridge.
谢谢你愿意跟我聊聊
I appreciate you talking to me.
等等  先别走
Wait, don't leave.
给你我的地址和电话号码
Um, I'm gonna give you my address and phone number.
还有几件事情
There are a couple of things
我明天去学校替你问问
I can check out for you tomorrow at school.
晚上给我打电话
Call in the evening.
谢谢
Thank you.
TW3呼叫总部
TW3 to control.
总部收到  TW3说吧
This is control, go ahead TW3.
开门  警察
Open up, police!
我说开门
I said open up!
我是莫洛夫斯基警探  理查德
This is Detective Morofsky, Richard.
把门打开
Open the door.
我去后面看看  萨姆
I'm out the back, Sam!
该死
Ah, dammit!
我们被耍了
We're fucked.
普兰蒂斯警监
Captain Prentis.
这是  汤姆·戴乐顿和尼尔
This is uh, Tom Dellerton and Neil?
-芬奇利  -芬奇利
- Finchley. - Finchley.
他们是约翰·韦斯福德的朋友
They were friends of John Wesford's
他们作了宣誓证词
and uh, they've made a sworn statement
证明三十一号晚上
that John was with them in San Diego
约翰和他们都在圣地亚哥
on the night of the 31st.
也就是西塞莉·图纳被杀当晚
When Cicely Tuner was murdered.
-真的是这样  -是的  长官
- Is that so? - Yes sir.
我们当时代表医学院
We were playing in a basketball tournament
参加篮球联赛
for medical students.
我们七个人周五晚上坐车去
Seven of us went down to train on Friday night
然后周日回来的
and came back Sunday.
你们住在哪儿
Where did you stay?
住高地酒店
At the Highland Inn.
我叔叔是那里的经理助理
My uncle's an assistant manager there.
他叫詹姆斯·芬奇利
James Finchley's his name.
韦斯福德一直和你们在一起吗
And Wesford was with you the whole time?
-是的  -从没离开过
- Yes, sir. - He never left your sight.
他离开的时间不可能赶回来
Not long enough for him to come all the way back here
并且杀了那个女孩
and murder that girl.
没错  新闻上说这些案子
Right, and we read that all these murders
全是一个人干的
were supposed to be the work of one man.
如果这个不是约翰干的
So if John didn't do that one,
别的案子也应该不是他干的
we figure he couldn't have done any of them.
没错
Right.
谢谢你们两位前来
I want to thank you boys for coming in.
感谢你们的帮助
We appreciate the help.
-不客气  长官  -谢谢
- You're welcome, sir. - Thanks.
通知萨姆  把那家伙带来
Call Sam, tell him to pick him up.
刚才通知过了
I already did a little while ago.
他们跟丢了
They lost him.
真该死
Goddamn!
快走  进去
Let's go. Inside!
是谁
Who is it?
你好
Howdy.
看够了没有  混蛋
Did you get an eyeful, asshole?
什么
What?
你刚才是不是在偷窥我
Did you get an eyeful?
站在窗外鬼鬼祟祟的
Out back, peeking through my window.
-什么时候  -就刚才
- When? - Just now.
关上门  锁好
Close your door and lock it.
真的不是你吗
You mean it wasn't you?
不管是谁已经跑了
Whoever was there is gone.
他长什么样
What did he look like?
不知道  只看到影子一晃
I don't know, I just saw a shadow.
你怎么来了
Why are you here?
后面这个人是谁
Who's the guy in the back?
-杰克  -杰克
- Jack. - Jack?
杰克杀了我弟弟
Jack killed my brother.
是谁
Who is it?
警察  莫斯卡莉小姐  开门好吗
Police, Miss Moscari, could you open up?
这么晚了是不是...
Isn't it a little late to be...
有紧急事件  能进去谈吗
This is an emergency, may we come in?
不太方便
I'm not really dressed.
没关系  我们是警察
It's OK, we're police officers.
你今晚和理查德·韦斯福德在一起
You were with Richard Wesford tonight?
是的
Yes.
他有没有说起要去哪
Did he tell you where he might be going,
他的打算
what his plans were?
没有
No.
你们都谈了些什么
What'd you talk about?
谈他的弟弟
About his brother.
你知道他现在在哪儿吗
Do you have any idea where he is now?
不  我不知道
No, I don't.
如果韦斯福德联系你
If Wesford contacts you,
请马上打这个电话告诉我们
would you call us at this number immediately?
他因为牵涉他弟弟的谋杀案被通缉
He's wanted in connection with his brother's murder.
我们有理由相信
We have reason to believe
他现在情绪失常  行事危险
he's emotionally disturbed and dangerous.
他弟弟死了
His brother's dead.
换做是你能不受影响吗
Wouldn't you be disturbed?
如果他联系你请告诉我们
Please call us if he contacts you.
他很危险
He's dangerous.
谢谢
Thank you.
照片上的这个人叫杰克·潘德勒
The man in the photograph's name is Jack Pendler.
也在我们诊所上班
He works at the clinic with us.
你能肯定是他吗
Are you sure he's the man?
知道他住哪儿吗
Do you know where he lives?
知道
Yeah.
等我一下  我换件衣服
I'll be right back, I'll get dressed.
-等等  -不
- Wait- - No.
我和你一起去
I'm coming with you.
等等  在那停一下
Wait, pull over there.
要干嘛
What for?
我去办点事
I gotta make a stop.
你要去哪儿
Where are you going?
到路对面一下
Right across the street.
我一会儿就回来  好吗
Be back in just a few minutes, all right?
-有什么事  -罗斯科让我来的
- What do you want? - Roscoe sent me.
出去
Beat it.
我在五十一页
I'm on page 51.
-说吧  -我要枪
- So? - I need a gun.
你这么帅的小伙子
Now what's a nice young man like you
要枪干嘛
want with a piece?
结婚贺礼
Wedding present.
钱带了吗
Show me something green.
你是警察吗
You a police officer?
不是
No.
那是法警
You a Federal Marshall?
财政部探员  联调局探员
A treasury agent? An agent of the FBI?
很好
Good.
你看起来很面熟
You look familiar.
我好像在哪见过你
I seen you around somewhere?
是吗
I don't know.
看过《豪门恩怨》吗
Watch Dynasty?
自己挑吧
Take your pick.
三百七十五一把
375.
开玩笑吧
You gotta be kidding me.
我从不拿钱开玩笑  伙计
I don't kid about money, pal.
等等
Come on.
就要这把  再来一盒子弹
I'll take this one and a box of shells.
我这没子弹
No bullets here.
要子弹到体育用品商店去
You want bullets, try a sporting goods store.
真是贴心
You're a real sweetheart.
好了  走吧
All right, let's go.
怎么了
What's the matter?
你干什么去了
Why did we stop here?
我去见一个人
I needed to see somebody.
我买了把枪
I bought a gun.
什么
What?
听着  不如你把地址给我
Listen, why don't you give me the address
接下去我自己搞定  好吗
and I'll take it alone from here, all right?
怎么  你要去杀了他吗
What, so you're gonna shoot him?
就算我想  也杀不了那个杂种
I couldn't shoot the motherfucker if I wanted to.
枪里没有子弹
I don't have any bullets.
没子弹
No bullets.
这家伙只卖抢  不卖子弹
The guy sells guns, he doesn't sell bullets.
真是太蠢了
Well that's pretty stupid,
没子弹要枪做什么
what good is a gun without any bullets?
你在这里做什么
What are you doing here?
西德尼
Sidney.
你  你吓到我了
You so, you scared me.
我忘了东西在这里
I forgot some of my, my stuff
我要用
and I needed it.
那你也不该在下班时间来
Well you're not supposed to be in here after hours.
尤其是发生过那件事以后
especially after what's already happened.
我明白
I understand.
我这就走
I was just leaving.
杰克
Jack?
先生
Sir?
我一直想告诉你
I've uh, I've been meaning to tell you.
你干得不错
You do good work.
谢谢您
Thank you, sir.
去找点乐子吧
Now go have some fun.
好的  先生
Yes, sir!
就是这里
That's it.
他一个人住吗
Does he live alone?
是的
Yeah.
他养狗吗
Do you know if he has a dog?
应该没有吧
I don't think so.
你有手电筒吗
Do you have a flashlight?
有  在杂物箱里
Yeah, in the glove compartment.
你要做什么
What are you gonna do?
就进去看看
Just take a look around.
你最好回家去
You better go home.
你怎么进去
How are you gonna get in?
我以前就干这个的
I used to do this for a living.
你要是回家的话
I'd feel a whole lot better about this
我会觉得好很多
if you'd go home.
回家吧
Go home.
你死定了  混蛋
You're gonna fry, motherfucker.
请求增援  完毕
Requesting backup, over.
不许动
Freeze!
手放在身后
All right, hands behind your back.
你有权保持沉默
You have the right to remain silent.
你所说的一切
Anything you say can and will be used against you
都将成为呈堂证供
in a court of law.
我记得人人都觉得
I remember everyone always thought
我嫉妒约翰
I was jealous of John.
这让我很生气
That pissed me off.
我
I...
我从没
I never...
我从没觉得嫉妒过他
I never thought I was.
有种说法
There's an old saying.
叫做有爱才会嫉妒
Where's there's no jealousy, there's no love.
你们昨晚真是把我们折腾得够呛
Well, you've given us quite a night.
潘德勒的真名叫做杰克·帕莫
Pendler's real name is Jack Parmel
他承认杀害了你弟弟
and he's confessed to the killing of your brother.
他说是出于自卫
He claims it was self-defense.
扯淡
It's bullshit.
你找到的他的医疗器具上的血迹
The blood on his medical instruments you found
和最后一个受害者丹妮丝·约翰逊的相符
matches the last victim, Denise Johnson.
帕莫说只是帮她做流产
Parmel claims he gave her an abortion
仅此而已
and that's all.
他说一定是你弟弟杀了她
He says your brother must've killed her.
但我们知道这是栽赃
But we know that's a frame.
六年前在俄亥俄州
Six years ago in Ohio,
他因强奸和故意伤害被捕
he was arrested for rape and aggravated assault.
然后他弃保潜逃了
He skipped bail and disappeared.
下午我们会指控他
We're arraigning him this afternoon
涉嫌六起谋杀
on six counts of murder.
谢谢
Thank you.
谢谢你
你的车到了  莫斯卡莉小姐
Your car is here now, Miss Moscari.
不介意的话  我可以送你回去
If you like, I could drive you home.
我自己可以
I can manage.
不过  谢谢
Thank you, though.
祝你好运
Good luck to you.
早日再会
I hope to see you soon.
-谢谢你  警长  -这边
- Thank you, Sergeant. - This way.
你确定这是有氧鞋吗
Are you sure these are aerobic shoes?
是的  您可以在进行有氧运动时穿
Yeah, you could use these for aerobics, sure.
好  就要这双
Fine, I'll take these.
选得好
Good choice.
-您要穿着吗  -是的
- Wanna wear 'em? - Yeah, I think I will.
♪自始至终♪
♪And through it all♪
♪即使疑惑♪
♪When there was doubt♪
♪我也克服了困难♪
♪I ate it up♪
♪战胜了困难♪
♪And spit it out♪
♪时间证明♪
♪The record shows♪
杰克归来
♪我经受住了磨难♪
♪I took the blows♪
杰克归来
♪并且用♪
♪And did it♪
♪自己的方式♪
♪My way♪
该死
Fuck!
该死的
Goddamn it!
该死
Fuck!
我要和你谈谈
I need to talk to you.
-理查德  -我要和你谈谈
- Richard. - I need to talk to you.
进来
Come in.
卡洛斯
Carlos!
没事的  妈
It's all right, mother.
回去睡吧
Go back to bed.
去我书房说
Let's go into my study.
我很不高兴你来我家  理查德
I'm very upset that you've come to my house, Richard.
这对我非常不尊重
It's very disrespectful to me.
已经这么晚了
It's very late at night,
你吓到了我母亲
you frightened my mother.
我还在做那样的梦
I'm still having the dreams.
我还在做那该死的梦
I'm still having the fucking dreams!
我知道你为什么来这里  理查德
I think I know why you're here, Richard.
你知道杰克·潘德勒不是开膛手
You know Jack Pendler isn't the Ripper.
他惯用右手也不吸烟
He's right-handed and he doesn't smoke.
我不知道
I don't know.
我觉得你知道真凶是谁  对吗
I think you know who the killer is, don't you?
什么
What?
对吗
Don't you?
不  我
No, I...
有些事情不对
Something's not right.
我想让你催眠我
I want you to hypnotize me.
理查德
Richard.
来吧  催眠我
Come on, hypnotize me.
求你了
Please.
拜托
好吧  我要你在椅子上放松
All right, I want you to relax in the chair.
放空思维
Clear your mind.
把注意力集中在光点上
Just concentrate only on the light,
仔细听我的声音
and listen carefully to my voice.
克莉丝
Chris!
加布里埃尔警长吗
Sergeant Gabriel?
我是卡洛斯·巴特拉
Carlos Battera.
西德尼
Sidney!
不
No.
开门  警察
Open up, it's the police!
快开门
Open up in there!
撞开
Break it down!
手举起来
Put your hands up!
♪Red harvest comes♪
♪Where can I run♪
♪Dancing high upon a ledge♪
♪Her laughter raining down♪
♪All of these falling leaves♪
♪The leaves wither and turn brown♪
♪Fate has brought us to this place♪
♪Come and take my hand♪
♪Years will come and go♪
♪Mountains crumble into sand♪
♪Red harvest comes♪
♪Where can I run♪
♪Stars forsake me♪
♪The cold wind shakes me down♪
♪Where can I run♪
♪Red harvest comes♪
♪Oh♪
♪Where can I run♪
♪Red harvest comes♪